Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the President, Beadle Administration Records 1916-1968
University of Chicago Library
- Series IB: General Files, I-Z
  - Research Institutes, Enrico Fermi Institute for Nuclear Studies, 1965-1968 (Box 287, Folder 1-2)
  - Research Institutes, Enrico Fermi Institute, the Laboratory for Astrophysics and Space Research, dedication, 1964-1968 (Box 287, Folder 3-4)
  - Research Institutes, Enrico Fermi Institute, the Laboratory for Astrophysics and Space Research, ground breaking, 1963-1964 (Box 287, Folder 5)
  - Research Institutes, industrial sponsors, 1961-1966 (Box 287, Folder 6)
  - Research Institutes, industrial sponsors, meetings, 1959-1961 (Box 287, Folder 7-8)
  - Research Institutes, industrial sponsors, meetings, 1961-1964 (Box 288, Folder 1-6)
  - Research Institutes, industrial sponsors, meetings, 1964-1968 (Box 289, Folder 1-3)
  - Research Institutes, Institute for the Study of Metals, (Ultra) Low Temperature Laboratory, 1955-1966 (Box 289, Folder 4)
  - Research Institutes, James Franck Institute, circa 1961 (Box 289, Folder 5)
  - Research Institutes, James Franck Institute, directorship, 1961-1968 (Box 289, Folder 6)
  - Research Institutes, Laboratory for Astrophysics and Space Research (LASR), 1964-1968 (Box 289, Folder 7)
  - Research Institutes, Laboratory for Astrophysics and Space Sciences, Samuelson and Sandquist, 1962 (Box 289, Folder 8)
  - Research Institutes, satellite and space probe missions, 1961-1968 (Box 289, Folder 9)
  - Research Institutes, space, 1961-1965 (Box 289, Folder 10)
  - Residential Planning, Committee on, report by Joseph R. Passonneau, 1964 (Box 289, Folder 11)
  - Retired professors registry, 1961-1968 (Box 290, Folder 1)
  - Retirement Committee, non-academic, 1961-1967 (Box 290, Folder 2)
  - Retirement expenses, 1961-1962 (Box 290, Folder 3)
  - Retirement income plan, 1961-1967 (Box 290, Folder 4-5)
  - Retirement income plan, non-academic, 1962-1968 (Box 290, Folder 6-7)
  - Retirement income plan, non-academic, supplementary allowances and postponed retirements, 1961-1968 (Box 290, Folder 8)
  - Retirement letters, non-academic, personnel, 1962-1965 (Box 291, Folder 1)
  - Retirement plans, 1963-1967 (Box 291, Folder 2)
  - Retirement Policy, Committee on, final report, 1962-1963 (Box 291, Folder 3)
  - Retirement Policy, Committee on, membership, 1961-1962 (Box 291, Folder 4)
  - Retirement Policy, Committee on, working papers, 1960-1962 (Box 291, Folder 5-6)
  - Retirements, non-academic, 1961-1962 (Box 291, Folder 7)
  - Retiring allowances, academic, 1961-1967 (Box 292, Folder 1)
  - Retiring allowances, non-academic, 1961-1968 (Box 292, Folder 2)
  - Review, disciplinary procedures, Kalven Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 292, Folder 3)
  - Rice University, Houston, Texas, 1961-1968 (Box 292, Folder 4)
  - Robie House Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 292, Folder 5-7)
  - Robie House, news clippings, restoration and fund raising, 1957-1968 (Box 292, Folder 8)
  - Robie House, restoration, 1959-1965 (Box 293, Folder 1)
  - Robie House, restoration and use, 1963-1964 (Box 293, Folder 2)
  - Rochester, University of, 1961-1968 (Box 293, Folder 3)
  - Rochester, University of, inauguration of President W. Allen Wallis, May 17, 1963 (Box 293, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller Memorial Chapel, 1961-1968 (Box 293, Folder 5-7)
  - Rockefeller Memorial Chapel, associate deanship and acting deanship, 1962-1965 (Box 294, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Memorial Chapel, deanship, Dr. Charles W. Gilkey, 1968 (Box 294, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller Memorial Chapel, deanship, installation of the dean, 1965 (Box 294, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller Memorial Chapel, public address system, 1947-1968 (Box 294, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller Public Service Awards, 1963-1964 (Box 294, Folder 5)
  - Rockwell, George Lincoln, 1962-1963 (Box 294, Folder 6)
  - Rollins College, Winter Park, Florida, 1968 (Box 294, Folder 7)
  - Romance Languages and Literatures, Department of, 1961-1968 (Box 294, Folder 8-9)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1949-1966 (Box 294, Folder 10)
  - Roosevelt University, 1957-1968 (Box 294, Folder 11-12)
  - Rosary College, 1967-1968 (Box 294, Folder 13)
  - Ross-McElroy Productions, 1961-1967 (Box 294, Folder 14)
  - Ross-McElroy Productions, "off-the-cuff" expedition, science, The University of Chicago Cancer Research, 1961-1962 (Box 294, Folder 15)
  - Ross-McElroy Productions, "off-the-cuff" program, A Great University Looks to the Future, May 6, 1962 (Box 295, Folder 1)
  - Rotary Clubs, 1955-1962 (Box 295, Folder 2)
  - Rush Graduate School of Medicine, 1968 (Box 295, Folder 3)
  - Rush Medical College, correspondence about dissolution of the University of Chicago and Rush, 1937-1962 (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Russia, 1961-1963 (Box 295, Folder 5)
  - Russia (Soviet), visitors from, 1964-1968 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Russia, Soviet Union, exchange program, Inter-University Committee on Travel Grants, 1960-1964 (Box 295, Folder 7)
  - Russia, Soviet Union, Inter-University Committee on Travel Grants, annual meeting, 1968 (Box 295, Folder 8)
  - Rutgers, the State University, New Jersey, 1964-1968 (Box 295, Folder 9)
  - S-, general, 1965-1968 (Box 295, Folder 10)
  - Saarinen, Eero, 1954-1964 (Box 295, Folder 11)
  - Saint Francis, the College of, Joilet, Illinois, 1967 (Box 295, Folder 12)
  - Saint Louis University, 1960-1965 (Box 295, Folder 13)
  - Saint Xavier College, 1961-1966 (Box 296, Folder 1)
  - Salaries, administrative, 1966-1968 (Box 296, Folder 2)
  - Salaries, wages and other compensations, faculty needs, 1955-1966 (Box 296, Folder 3)
  - Salaries, wages and other compensations, faculty salaries1951-1965 (Box 296, Folder 4)
  - Salaries, wages and other compensations, faculty salaries and compensations, 1960-1964 (Box 296, Folder 5-6)
  - Salaries, wages and other compensations, Harvard survey on faculty compensation, recruitment and retention, 1967 (Box 296, Folder 7)
  - Salaries, wages and other compensations, Harvard survey on faculty compensation, recruitment and retention, 1967 (Box 297, Folder 1-2)
  - Salaries, wages and other compensations, limits of authority, 1965-1966 (Box 297, Folder 3)
  - Salaries, wages and other compensations, other schools, 1965-1967 (Box 297, Folder 4)
  - Salk Institute for Biological Studies, San Diego, California, 1962-1967 (Box 297, Folder 5)
  - Salzburg Seminar, 1961-1968 (Box 297, Folder 6-7)
  - Sarah Lawrence College, 1961-1965 (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Saturday Review magazine, 1963-1968 (Box 297, Folder 9)
  - Saturday seminars, 1961-1967 (Box 297, Folder 10)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, 1961-1965 (Box 297, Folder 11-12)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, 1961-1968 (Box 298, Folder 1-3)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, American Council of Learned Societies, 1962 (Box 298, Folder 4)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1961-1965 (Box 298, Folder 5)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, Coman, Seymour, 1961 (Box 298, Folder 6)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, Fulbright-Hays program, 1961-1967 (Box 298, Folder 7)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, Fulbright-Hays program, university recipients of awards, 1961-1968 (Box 298, Folder 8)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, Hay, John Fellows program, Hay Fellows Alumni Association, 1966 (Box 298, Folder 9)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, National Science Foundation, 1966-1968 (Box 298, Folder 10)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, performance scholarships of the Department of Music, 1962-1966 (Box 298, Folder 11)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, post-PhD., 1952-1967 (Box 298, Folder 12-13)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, Rhodes, 1946-1968 (Box 298, Folder 14)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, Trustee program, 1964-1968 (Box 298, Folder 15)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, University Scholars program, 1962-1966 (Box 298, Folder 16)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, White House fellowships, 1964-1968 (Box 298, Folder 17)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, Wilson, Woodrow National Fellowship Foundation Program, 1965-1968 (Box 299, Folder 1)
  - Scholarships and fellowships, Witco Chemical Company Graduate Fellowship in Chemistry, 1964 (Box 299, Folder 2)
  - Schn-, general, 1963-1966 (Box 299, Folder 3)
  - Science and Human Affairs, Committee on, 1962-1963 (Box 299, Folder 4)
  - Science, a publication of the American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1961-1966 (Box 299, Folder 5)
  - Science and public affairs, colloquium on, 1963 (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Science and university affairs, 1965-1966 (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - Scientific American, 1965-1968 (Box 299, Folder 8)
  - Scott, Mrs. Ernest Lyman, 1965-1967 (Box 299, Folder 9)
  - Se-, general, 1964-1968 (Box 299, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of the Board of Trustees, 1961-1968 (Box 299, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of the University, 1951-1963 (Box 299, Folder 12)
  - Security, 1961-1966 (Box 299, Folder 13)
  - Security, Committee on, 1965-1967 (Box 299, Folder 14)
  - Security, Interstate Service Corporation, 1965-1968 (Box 299, Folder 15)
  - Selection of a dean for Rockefeller Memorial Chapel, Committee on the, 1961-1965 (Box 299, Folder 16-17)
  - Selective Service, deferment requests, 1961-1968 (Box 300, Folder 1)
  - Selective Service, demonstrations, Students Against the Rank (SAR) study-in, statements and policies, 1966-1967 (Box 300, Folder 2)
  - Selective Service, general, 1960-1968 (Box 300, Folder 3-4)
  - Selective Service, International Conference, papers read, December 4-7, 1966 (Box 300, Folder 5-6)
  - Selective Service, procedures, policy statements, 1967-1968 (Box 301, Folder 1)
  - Selective Service, procedures, policy and statements, student sit-in demonstration, 1966 (Box 301, Folder 2)
  - Selective Service, procedures, policy and statements, student sit-in demonstration, 1966 (Box 301, Folder 3)
  - Selective Service, procedures, sit-in, faculty and trustees, comments, 1966 (Box 301, Folder 4)
  - Selective Service, procedures, sit-in, letters of commendation to the University of Chicago personnel, 1966 (Box 301, Folder 5)
  - Selective Service, procedures, student announcements, sit-in demonstration, 1966-1967 (Box 301, Folder 6)
  - Selective Service, procedures, student sit-in demonstrations, clippings, 1966-1968 (Box 301, Folder 7)
  - Selective Service, procedures, student sit-in demonstrations, Maroon clippings, 1966-1967 (Box 302, Folder 1)
  - Selective Service, procedures, student sit-in demonstrations, outside comments, 1966-1968 (Box 302, Folder 2-3)
  - Selective Service and Related Matters, International Conference on, 1966-1967 (Box 302, Folder 4)
  - Selective Service Scientific Advisory Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 302, Folder 5)
  - Selective Service, sit-in, 1966 (Box 302, Folder 6)
  - Selective Service, Student-Faculty Committee on Ranking Policy, 1966-1967 (Box 302, Folder 7)
  - Selective Service, Student-Faculty Committee on Ranking Policy, Dunham Committee, 1966 (Box 303, Folder 1)
  - Selective Service, Student-Faculty Committee on Ranking Policy, Fiske Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 303, Folder 2)
  - Selective Service, Students Against the Rank (SAR), 1967-1968 (Box 303, Folder 3)
  - Selective Service, Vietnam special assembly, 1967-1968 (Box 303, Folder 4)
  - Seven Universities meetings, 1961 (Box 303, Folder 5)
  - Sh-, general, 1964-1966 (Box 303, Folder 6)
  - Shakespeare and the Renaissance, Festival of, 1964 (Box 303, Folder 7)
  - Shimer College, 1961-1968 (Box 303, Folder 8)
  - Shockley, Dr. William, 1965-1968 (Box 303, Folder 9)
  - Singapore, University of, 1962-1963 (Box 303, Folder 10)
  - Singapore, University of, Lewis, H.D. registrar, 1963 (Box 303, Folder 11)
  - Size of the University of Chicago, Sub-Committee to Study, 1959-1963 (Box 303, Folder 12)
  - Slavic Area Studies, Committee on, 1961-1968 (Box 303, Folder 13)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures, Department of, 1961-1965 (Box 303, Folder 14)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures, Department of, 1965-1968 (Box 304, Folder 1)
  - Sm-, general, 1968 (Box 304, Folder 2)
  - Sn-, general, 1963-1968 (Box 304, Folder 3)
  - Social Sciences, Division of the, 1951-1968 (Box 304, Folder 4-8)
  - Social Sciences, Division of the, Committee on General Studies, 1962-1963 (Box 304, Folder 9)
  - Social Sciences, Division of the, space, 1961-1968 (Box 304, Folder 10)
  - Social Sciences, Division of the, visiting committee, 1962-1964 (Box 304, Folder 11)
  - Social Sciences, Division of the, visiting committee, 1965-1968 (Box 304, Folder 12)
  - Social Sciences, International Encyclopedia of the, 1960-1968 (Box 304, Folder 13)
  - Social Sciences, pamphlets and magazines, 1927-1964 (Box 305, Folder 1)
  - Social Sciences Visiting Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 305, Folder 2)
  - Social Service Administration, School of, 1961-1968 (Box 305, Folder 3-7)
  - Social Service Administration, School of, accreditation, 1961-1967 (Box 305, Folder 8)
  - Social Service Administration, School of, brief history, 1926-1963 (Box 305, Folder 9)
  - Social Service Administration, School of, Conference on Guaranteed Minimum Income, 1966 (Box 305, Folder 10)
  - Social Service Administration, School of, space, 1961-1965 (Box 305, Folder 11)
  - Social Service Administration, School of, student trip to Germany, July 1962 (Box 305, Folder 12)
  - Social Service Administration, Visiting Committee on, 1961-1968 (Box 305, Folder 13)
  - Social Thought, Committee on, 1961-1968 (Box 306, Folder 1-5)
  - Social Thought, Committee on, Center for International Understanding, Paris, proposed, 1958-1967 (Box 306, Folder 6)
  - Social Thought, Committee on, chairmanship, 1964-1968 (Box 306, Folder 7)
  - Social Thought, Committee on, conference "Towards World Community," 1966 (Box 306, Folder 8)
  - Social Thought, Committee on, facilities and space, 1955-1965 (Box 306, Folder 9)
  - Social Thought, Committee on, scholarships and fellowships, 1965 (Box 306, Folder 10)
  - Society for Religion in Higher Education, 1964-1966 (Box 306, Folder 11)
  - Sociology, Department of, 1961-1962 (Box 306, Folder 12-13)
  - Sociology, Department of, 1962-1968 (Box 307, Folder 1-3)
  - Sociology, Department of, space, 1964-1965 (Box 307, Folder 4)
  - Sorensen, Theodore (Ted), 1965-1966 (Box 307, Folder 5)
  - South Asia Language and Area Center, 1960-1968 (Box 307, Folder 6)
  - South Asia Language and Area Center, technical reports, 1967-1968 (Box 307, Folder 7)
  - South Asian Languages and Civilizations, Department of, 1962-1968 (Box 307, Folder 8)
  - South Asian Studies, Committee on, 1961-1962 (Box 307, Folder 9)
  - South Campus, Committee on, 1967-1968 (Box 307, Folder 10)
  - South Campus, Committee on, south campus urban renewal plan, 1965-1968 (Box 307, Folder 11)
  - South Carolina, University of, 1967-1968 (Box 307, Folder 12)
  - South East Chicago Commission, 1961-1965 (Box 308, Folder 1-7)
  - South East Chicago Commission, 1964-1965 (Box 309, Folder 1)
  - South East Chicago Commission, annual meetings, 1961-1967 (Box 309, Folder 2)
  - South East Chicago Commission, Board of Directors, meetings, membership, 1961-1968 (Box 309, Folder 3-5)
  - South East Chicago Commission, Executive Committee, meetings, 1961-1968 (Box 309, Folder 6-7)
  - South East Chicago Commission, Hyde Park-Kenwood urban renewal plan, 1968-1966 (Box 309, Folder 8)
  - South East Chicago Commission, security, 1955-1965 (Box 309, Folder 9)
  - South East Chicago Commission, south campus plan, 1961-1968 (Box 310, Folder 1-3)
  - South East Chicago Commission, William Zeckendorg, Webb and Knapp, 1955-1966 (Box 310, Folder 4)
  - South Park Improvement Association, 1961-1964 (Box 310, Folder 5)
  - South Shore Community, organizations and activities, 1960-1968 (Box 310, Folder 6)
  - South West Hyde Park Neighborhood, Redevelopment Corporation, 1962 (Box 310, Folder 7-8)
  - South West Hyde Park Neighborhood, Redevelopment Corporation, 1963-1967 (Box 311, Folder 1-6)
  - South West Hyde Park Neighborhood, Redevelopment Corporation, Board of Directors, notices and minutes, 1956-1962 (Box 312, Folder 1)
  - Southern Asian Studies, Committee on, 1961-1967 (Box 312, Folder 2-4)
  - Southern Asian Studies, Committee on, Asian Arts Series, 1962-1963 (Box 312, Folder 5)
  - Southern Asian Studies, Committee on, Asian Arts Series, publicity, 1962-1963 (Box 312, Folder 6)
  - Southern Association of College and University Business Officers, 1961-1965 (Box 312, Folder 7)
  - Southern California, University of, 1961-1967 (Box 312, Folder 8-9)
  - Southern Illinois University, 1961-1964 (Box 312, Folder 10)
  - Southern Methodist University, 1961-1963 (Box 312, Folder 11)
  - Southside Community Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 313, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Bloc, forthcoming scientific and technical meetings in the, 1963-1968 (Box 313, Folder 2-3)
  - Sp-, general, 1963-1966 (Box 313, Folder 4)
  - Space, classrooms, 1962-1967 (Box 313, Folder 5)
  - Space, needs, 1961-1967 (Box 313, Folder 6)
  - Space and Related Sciences, Committee on, 1961 (Box 313, Folder 7)
  - Space Study, Faculty Committee on, 1961-1963 (Box 313, Folder 8-9)
  - Space, Study of Utilization of Instructional Facilities at the University of Chicago, conducted by Michigan State University, 1959-1963 (Box 313, Folder 10)
  - Space, Study of Utilization of Instructional Facilities at the University of Chicago, conducted by Michigan State University, 1959-1963 (Box 314, Folder 1)
  - Speakers, Committee on, Speakers Bureau, 1964-1965 (Box 314, Folder 2)
  - Special reports, Office of the President, The University of Chicago, 1965 (Box 314, Folder 3)
  - Sports Illustrated, a publication, 1961-1968 (Box 314, Folder 4)
  - St-, general, 1965-1968 (Box 314, Folder 5)
  - Stagg, Amos Alonzo, Field, old demolition of north and west stands, 1950-1967 (Box 314, Folder 6)
  - Stanford University, 1961-1968 (Box 314, Folder 7-11)
  - Stanford University, gift information exchange, 1961-1968 (Box 314, Folder 12)
  - Stanford University, Sterling's speech, Executives' Club of Chicago, 1961 (Box 314, Folder 13)
  - Stanford University, Winds of Freedom Foundation, 1965-1968 (Box 314, Folder 14)
  - State of the University, 1962-1965 (Box 314, Folder 15)
  - State of the University, 1963-1965 (Box 315, Folder 1)
  - State of the University, background material, 1958-1962 (Box 315, Folder 2)
  - State of the University, President's address to students, 1966-1967 (Box 315, Folder 3)
  - State of the University, the President's Reflections, George Wells Beadle, background material, 1967-1968 (Box 315, Folder 4)
  - State of the University, The President's Report, 1965-1967 (Box 315, Folder 5)
  - State of the University, The President's Report, background material, 1964-1966 (Box 315, Folder 6-7)
  - State of the University, reports, 1961-1968 (Box 316, Folder 1-3)
  - Statistical information, University of Chicago, 1963 (Box 316, Folder 4)
  - Statistics, 1960-1963 (Box 316, Folder 5)
  - Statistics, college applications, 1945-1968 (Box 316, Folder 6)
  - Statistics, Committee on, 1951-1961 (Box 316, Folder 7)
  - Statistics, Department of, 1961-1968 (Box 316, Folder 8-10)
  - Statistics, Department of, chairmanship, 1963-1966 (Box 316, Folder 11)
  - Statistics, miscellaneous, 1961-1965 (Box 316, Folder 12)
  - Statistics, other schools, 1961-1963 (Box 316, Folder 13)
  - Statistics, outside publications, 1964-1968 (Box 316, Folder 14)
  - Statistics, Time survey of college students, 1961 (Box 316, Folder 15)
  - Statistics, the University of Chicago and the Community, Town and Gown, 1964 (Box 316, Folder 16)
  - Statutes, by-laws and articles of incorporation, 1965-1968 (Box 317, Folder 1)
  - Statutes Concerning the Instructorship and Assistant Professorship, Committee on, 1962-1964 (Box 317, Folder 2)
  - Stevenson, Adlai E. Memorial, Institute of International Affairs, 1966-1968 (Box 317, Folder 3)
  - Stevenson, Adlai E. Memorial, Institute of International Affairs, agreement on use of Robie House, 1966-1968 (Box 317, Folder 4)
  - Stevenson, Adlai E. Memorial, Institute of International Affairs, directorship, 1966-1968 (Box 317, Folder 5)
  - Stevenson, Adlai E. Memorial, Institute of International Affairs, financing and site, 1965-1967 (Box 317, Folder 6-7)
  - Sto-, general, 1965-1967 (Box 317, Folder 8)
  - Stochastics, 1961-1968 (Box 317, Folder 9)
  - Student Advisory Committees, councils and groups, 1967-1968 (Box 317, Folder 10)
  - Student aid, 1961-1965 (Box 317, Folder 11)
  - Student aid, 1962-1968 (Box 318, Folder 1)
  - Student Bill of Rights, 1963-1968 (Box 318, Folder 2)
  - Student complaint, housing, registration, 1965-1968 (Box 318, Folder 3)
  - Student demonstrations, Administration Building, department heads, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 4)
  - Student demonstrations, chronology, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 5)
  - Student demonstrations, clippings, general, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 6)
  - Student demonstrations, College Council, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 7)
  - Student demonstrations, Dunham, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 8)
  - Student demonstrations, faculty, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 9)
  - Student demonstrations, Maroon, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 10)
  - Student demonstrations, proposal, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 11)
  - Student demonstrations, ranking, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 12)
  - Student demonstrations, security, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 13)
  - Student demonstrations, Selective Service, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 14)
  - Student demonstrations, spokesman W. Blum, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 15)
  - Student demonstrations, statements, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 16)
  - Student demonstrations, student government, general, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 17)
  - Student demonstrations, student unrest, general, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 18)
  - Student demonstrations, Students Against the Rank (SAR), general, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 19)
  - Student demonstrations, Students Against the Rank (SAR), letters, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 20)
  - Student demonstrations, University Council, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 21)
  - Student demonstrations, university procedure and policy, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 22)
  - Student demonstrations, University Senate, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 23)
  - Student directory, 1961-1962 (Box 318, Folder 24)
  - Student draft demonstration, statements and clips on, 1966 (Box 318, Folder 25)
  - Student draft demonstration, statements and clips on, 1966 (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Student Faculty Administration Court, 1966-1968 (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - Student government, charter flights, 1961-1966 (Box 319, Folder 3)
  - Student government, organizations and activities, 1961-1965 (Box 319, Folder 4-8)
  - Student government, organizations and activities, 1966-1967 (Box 320, Folder 1-3)
  - Student government, organizations and activities, Art Student Association, 1967 (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - Student government, organizations and activities, Conference on the City and the University, 1967 (Box 320, Folder 5)
  - Student government, organizations and activities, Congress on Racial Equality (CORE), 1962-1964 (Box 320, Folder 6)
  - Student government, organizations and activities, student tutors elementary project, 1967 (Box 320, Folder 7)
  - Student government, organizations and activities, student Woodlawn area project, 1963-1968 (Box 320, Folder 8)
  - Student government, organizations and activities, Students for a Democratic Society, protest, 1967 (Box 320, Folder 9)
  - Student government, organizations and activities, WHPK, WUCB radio station, 1961-1968 (Box 320, Folder 10-11)
  - Student Health Organization of Chicago, 1966-1968 (Box 320, Folder 12)
  - Student organizations, Order of the Coif, 1958-1968 (Box 321, Folder 1)
  - Student recruitment, 1961-1968 (Box 321, Folder 2-3)
  - Student recruitment, black, 1963-1968 (Box 321, Folder 4)
  - Student recruitment, black, demands on admission, housing, media and outside comment, 1968 (Box 321, Folder 5)